Powder Keg is a action, war film directed by Alejandro González Iñárritu.
The Driver is drafted by the UN to rescue a wounded war photographer
named Harvey Jacobs from out of hostile territory.
While they are leaving Jacobs tells the Driver about the horrors he saw as a
photographer, but he regrets his inability to help war victims.
Jacobs answers the driver curiosity about why he is a
photographer by saying how his mother taught him to see.
He gives the Driver the film needed for a New York Times story
and also his dog tags to give to his mother.
When they reach the border, they are confronted by a guard who begins to draw arms
as Jacobs begins taking pictures, trying to get himself killed.
The Driver drives through a hail of gunfire to the border, but
finds Jacobs killed by a bullet through the seat.
The Driver arrives in America to visit Jacobs' mother and share the news of him winning the
Pulitzer prize and hand over the dog tags, only to discover that she is blind.
The Driver, played by Clive Owen.
Harvey Jacobs, played by Stellan Skarsgård.
Mother, played by Lois Smith.
Paramilitary 1, played by Javier Zaragoza.
Paramilitary 2, played by Luis Francisco Escobedo.
Paramilitary 3, played by Gilberto Barraza.
The BMW film series The Hire consists of eight short films (averaging about ten
minutes each) produced for internet distribution in 2001 and 2002.
A form of branded content, the shorts were directed by popular filmmakers from around the globe and starred
Clive Owen as "the Driver" while highlighting the performance aspects of various BMW automobiles.
The series made a comeback in 2016, fourteen years after its original run ended.